

Dorian-Ioan VELICI

O Home: Spl. 1 Decembrie 1918, bl. 29, ap. 16, 305500, Lugoj, Romania

Email: dorian.ioan_velici@hotmail.com Phone: (+40) 720390573

Website: https://dorian-ioan-velici.github.io/personal-website/index.html

WhatsApp Messenger: +40 720 390 573

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/dorian-ioan-velici/

Gender: Male Date of birth: 15/12/1996 Nationality: Romanian

ABOUT ME

I am a problem-solving person. Both in my personal & professional space, I particularly enjoy using my skills to solve challenging problems, to future improve processes and to prevent less desired outcomes from occuring.

By working at FORVIA Hella Lugoj as a Technical Assistant in the Backend Area, I gained on-field experience, developed my general knowledge and analytical skills around PCB-testing equipments, CNC routing machines & automatic soldering stations by configuring / maintaining the equipments, optimizing / redesigning the programs and, finally - improving the overall manufacturing processes.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

[01/10/2017 - 01/07/2021]

Information Technology Engineer

"Ioan Slavici" University - Faculty of Engineering

City: Timișoara | **Country:** Romania

WORK EXPERIENCE

[11/10/2024 - Current] Website Developer

City: Lugoj | Country: Romania

Website development - both programming & designing web pages.

[27/04/2023 – Current]

Technical Assistant (Backend Area)

FORVIA Hella https://www.hella.com/hella-ro/

City: Lugoj | Country: Romania | Email address: dorianioan.velici@forvia.com | Name of unit or department: PCB Production (Backend Area) | Business or sector: Manufacturing

My usual tasks consist in:

- regular analytical & problem-solving activities;
- technical maintenance and equipment repair;
- program optimization / redesign for many essential devices used at PCB-manufacturing processes.

The equipments I'm most familiar with:

- ICT/EOL teststands (Aeroflex 4250 & National Instruments NI LabVIEW), Takaya Flying Probe Tester:
- automatic selective soldering machines (SEHO SelectLine C systems);
- CNC routing machines used in the PCB depaneling process (Schunk & Asys Divisio 2000 Ergo millings);
- Maestro 4S cutting stations;
- plus other PCB-manufacturing factory equipments.

[02/06/2015 – Current] **IT Technician**

City: Lugoj | Country: Romania

- Configure, upgrade & optimize Windows OS-based systems;
- Troubleshoot & fix hardware failures:

- Improve the overall performance, gain stability & fix problems caused by software-related issues.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Romanian

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING C1 READING C1 WRITING C1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DRIVING LICENCE

Motorbikes: AM

Cars: B

DIGITAL SKILLS

My Digital Skills

NI LabVIEW | Computer Literacy | SAP ERP | PCB Debugging | Process Optimization | CNC Programming | Process Failure Mode Effects Analysis | Website Development